districtspeed.com 2018-12-14

# Privacy Policy – District Speed

Privacy Policy

Protecting your private information is our priority. This Statement of Privacy applies to the www.districtspeed.com and DistrictSpeed and governs data collection and usage. For the purposes of this Privacy Policy, unless otherwise noted, all references to DistrictSpeed include www.districtspeed.com and DistrictSpeed. The DistrictSpeed website is a News and information site. By using the DistrictSpeed website, you consent to the data practices described in this statement.

Collection of your Personal Information

DistrictSpeed may collect personally identifiable information, such as your name. If you purchase DistrictSpeed’s products and services, we collect billing and credit card information. This information is used to complete the purchase transaction. DistrictSpeed may also collect anonymous demographic information, which is not unique to you, such as your age and gender. We may gather additional personal or non-personal information in the future.

Information about your computer hardware and software may be automatically collected by DistrictSpeed. This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring website addresses. This information is used for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of the DistrictSpeed website.

DistrictSpeed encourages you to review the privacy statements of websites you choose to link to from DistrictSpeed so that you can understand how those websites collect, use and share your information. DistrictSpeed is not responsible for the privacy statements or other content on websites outside of the DistrictSpeed website.

Use of your Personal Information

DistrictSpeed collects and uses your personal information to operate its website(s) and deliver the services you have requested.

DistrictSpeed may also use your personally identifiable information to inform you of other products or services available from DistrictSpeed and its affiliates. DistrictSpeed may also contact you via surveys to conduct research about your opinion of current services or of potential new services that may be offered.

DistrictSpeed does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties.

DistrictSpeed may, from time to time, contact you on behalf of external business partners about a particular offering that may be of interest to you. In those cases, your unique personally identifiable information (e-mail, name, address, telephone number) is not transferred to the third party. DistrictSpeed may share data with trusted partners to help perform statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries. All such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to DistrictSpeed, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information.

DistrictSpeed may keep track of the websites and pages our users visit within DistrictSpeed, in order to determine what DistrictSpeed services are the most popular. This data is used to deliver customized content and advertising within DistrictSpeed to customers whose behavior indicates that they are interested in a particular subject area.

DistrictSpeed will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on DistrictSpeed or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of DistrictSpeed; and, (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of DistrictSpeed, or the public.

Security of your Personal Information

To secure your personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure, DistrictSpeed uses the following:

cloudflare.com

When personal information (such as a credit card number) is transmitted to other websites, it is protected through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) protocol.

Children Under Thirteen

DistrictSpeed does not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of thirteen. If you are under the age of thirteen, you must ask your parent or guardian for permission to use this website.

Disconnecting your DistrictSpeed Account from Third Party Websites

You will be able to connect your DistrictSpeed account to third party accounts. BY CONNECTING YOUR DistrictSpeed ACCOUNT TO YOUR THIRD PARTY ACCOUNT, YOU ACKNOWLEDGE AND AGREE THAT YOU ARE CONSENTING TO THE CONTINUOUS RELEASE OF INFORMATION ABOUT YOU TO OTHERS (IN ACCORDANCE WITH YOUR PRIVACY SETTINGS ON THOSE THIRD PARTY SITES). IF YOU DO NOT WANT INFORMATION ABOUT YOU, INCLUDING PERSONALLY IDENTIFYING INFORMATION, TO BE SHARED INTHIS MANNER, DO NOT USE THE THIS FEATURE. You may disconnect your account from a third party account at any time. Users may learn how to disconnect their accounts from third-party websites by visiting their “My Account” page. Users may also contact us via email or telephone..

Opt-Out & Unsubscribe

We respect your privacy and give you an opportunity to opt-out of receiving announcements of certain information. Users may opt-out of receiving any or all communications from DistrictSpeed by contacting us here:

– Web page: districtspeed.com

– Email: fb@districtspeed.com

Changes to this Statement

DistrictSpeed will occasionally update this Statement of Privacy to reflect company and customer feedback. DistrictSpeed encourages you to periodically review this Statement to be informed of how DistrictSpeed is protecting your information.

Contact Information

DistrictSpeed welcomes your questions or comments regarding this Statement of Privacy. If you believe that DistrictSpeed has not adhered to this Statement, please contact DistrictSpeed at:

DistrictSpeed

Email Address:

fb@districtspeed.com

Effective as of May 01, 2014
